<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Blog Today</title>
    <link>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Blog Today</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:45:09 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connected</title>
      <link>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/connected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:45:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/connected/</guid>
      <description>The thing now becoming increasing important is control over where we put our attention. We can hide from each other even if we are constantly connected to each other.
&amp;ldquo;When I ask people, what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with having a conversation, people say, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with having a conversation. It takes place in real time. And you can&amp;rsquo;t control what you&amp;rsquo;re gonna say.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;So that&amp;rsquo;s the bottom line. texting, email posting all of these things let us present the self as we want to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When You&#39;re a Kid</title>
      <link>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:14:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/kid/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re a kid, everything is astonishing. Everything is new. And so your brain is awake and turned on. So every second, your brain is learning something new: how the world works. And so the muscle of your brain is activated.
And as you get older and your brain has figured out the patterns of how the world works: this is how you make money; this is how you graduate school; this is how you get a mortgage; this is how you have kids&amp;hellip; And once your brain establishes a routine, it stops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Floating World</title>
      <link>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/floating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 19:09:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/floating/</guid>
      <description>“Living only for the moment, turning our attention to the pleasures of the moon, the snow, the cherry blossoms and the maples, singing songs, drinking wine and diverting ourselves in just floating, floating, caring not a whit for the poverty staring us in the face, refusing to be disheartened, like a gourd floating along with the river current: this is what we call the floating world.”
From A Tale of the Floating World, by Asai Rydi, about 1665 (translated by Richard Lane)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shi&#39;s Understanding of Procrastination</title>
      <link>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/shi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:34:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/shi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The worst thing about procrastination is not to delay, but to make yourself hesitant or even lose confidence.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Whatever you do, decide, and do it right away, which in itself makes people lively and maintains a sense of initiative and happiness.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oscar</title>
      <link>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/oscar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 18:44:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theheartisan.github.io/en/blogs/oscar/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Political correctness&amp;rdquo; was quietly discussed at the time of the victory of &amp;ldquo;Everything Everywhere All at Once&amp;rdquo;. This view arose early when Moonlight Boy won the award that year; after all, it was another hard look at the rise of minorities.
Some people say that &amp;ldquo;political correctness&amp;rdquo; is the biggest source of antipathy for hypocrisy - a polite and friendly way to give way to smiling may follow the social identity of &amp;ldquo;good citizens,&amp;rdquo; as to the extent to which this act of kindness is due to &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; is hard to know.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
